Special subset sums: optimum
http://projecteuler.net/problem=103
Let S(A) represent the sum of elements in set A of size n. We shall call it a special sum set if for any two non-empty disjoint subsets, B and C, the following properties are true:
S(B) ≠ S(C); that is, sums of subsets cannot be equal.
If B contains more elements than C then S(B) > S(C).
If S(A) is minimised for a given n, we shall call it an optimum special sum set. The first five optimum special sum sets are given below.
n = 1: 1n = 2: 1, 2n = 3: 2, 3, 4n = 4: 3, 5, 6, 7n = 5: 6, 9, 11, 12, 13
It seems that for a given optimum set, A = a1, a2, ... , an, the next optimum set is of the form B = b, a1+b, a2+b, ... ,an+b, where b is the "middle" element on the previous row.
By applying this "rule" we would expect the optimum set for n = 6 to be A = 11, 17, 20, 22, 23, 24, with S(A) = 117. However, this is not the optimum set, as we have merely applied an algorithm to provide a near optimum set. The optimum set for n = 6 is A = 11, 18, 19, 20, 22, 25, with S(A) = 115 and corresponding set string: 111819202225.
Given that A is an optimum special sum set for n = 7, find its set string.
NOTE: This problem is related to Problem 105 and Problem 106.