Cuboid layers
http://projecteuler.net/problem=126
The minimum number of cubes to cover every visible face on a cuboid measuring 3 x 2 x 1 is twenty-two.
If we then add a second layer to this solid it would require forty-six cubes to cover every visible face, the third layer would require seventy-eight cubes, and the fourth layer would require one-hundred and eighteen cubes to cover every visible face.
However, the first layer on a cuboid measuring 5 x 1 x 1 also requires twenty-two cubes; similarly the first layer on cuboids measuring 5 x 3 x 1, 7 x 2 x 1, and 11 x 1 x 1 all contain forty-six cubes.
We shall define C(n) to represent the number of cuboids that contain n cubes in one of its layers. So C(22) = 2, C(46) = 4, C(78) = 5, and C(118) = 8.
It turns out that 154 is the least value of n for which C(n) = 10.
Find the least value of n for which C(n) = 1000.