Firecracker
http://projecteuler.net/problem=317
A firecracker explodes at a height of 100 m above level ground. It breaks into a large number of very small fragments, which move in every direction; all of them have the same initial velocity of 20 m/s.
We assume that the fragments move without air resistance, in a uniform gravitational field with g=9.81 m/s2.
Find the volume (in m3) of the region through which the fragments move before reaching the ground.
Give your answer rounded to four decimal places.