Sum of a square and a cube
http://projecteuler.net/problem=348
Many numbers can be expressed as the sum of a square and a cube. Some of them in more than one way.
Consider the palindromic numbers that can be expressed as the sum of a square and a cube, both greater than 1, in exactly 4 different ways.
For example, 5229225 is a palindromic number and it can be expressed in exactly 4 different ways:
22852 + 203
22232 + 663
18102 + 1253
11972 + 1563
Find the sum of the five smallest such palindromic numbers.