Platonic Dice
http://projecteuler.net/problem=389
An unbiased single 4-sided die is thrown and its value, T, is noted.T unbiased 6-sided dice are thrown and their scores are added together. The sum, C, is noted.C unbiased 8-sided dice are thrown and their scores are added together. The sum, O, is noted.O unbiased 12-sided dice are thrown and their scores are added together. The sum, D, is noted.D unbiased 20-sided dice are thrown and their scores are added together. The sum, I, is noted.
Find the variance of I, and give your answer rounded to 4 decimal places.