Rhombus Tilings
http://projecteuler.net/problem=594
For a polygon P, let t(P) be the number of ways in which P can be tiled using rhombi and squares with edge length 1. Distinct rotations and reflections are counted as separate tilings.
For example, if O is a regular octagon with edge length 1, then t(O) = 8. As it happens, all these 8 tilings are rotations of one another:
Let O_a,b be the equal-angled convex octagon whose edges alternate in length between a and b.
For example, here is O_2,1, with one of its tilings:
You are given that t(O_1,1)=8, t(O_2,1)=76 and t(O_3,2)=456572.
Find t(O_4,2).