Prime pair sets
http://projecteuler.net/problem=60
The primes 3, 7, 109, and 673, are quite remarkable. By taking any two primes and concatenating them in any order the result will always be prime. For example, taking 7 and 109, both 7109 and 1097 are prime. The sum of these four primes, 792, represents the lowest sum for a set of four primes with this property.
Find the lowest sum for a set of five primes for which any two primes concatenate to produce another prime.